Albert E. Moss Collection 1990.0031
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series V: Visual Materials, undated, 1920-1965
  - Subseries C: Photographic prints, 1920-1965
    - Red Oak, "big oak" above Lake Mashapaug forestry camp, Union, Connecticut, undated (Box 14)
    - Fire plots, Fenton River, Gurleyville, Connecticut, 1935; 4 photographic prints (Box 14)
    - Fire plots, Mason's Mill unit, undated; 2 photographic prints (Box 14)
    - 20 year old burn come up to poplar, poor growth, undated (Box 14)
    - White pine and hemlocks, Mansfield Depot, Connecticut, 1933; 2 photographic prints (Box 14)
    - Thinning Pine Acres farm, Hampton, Connecticut, 1935-1962; 22 photographic prints (Box 14)
    - Selective logging in Long Leaf Pine, note high wheels and oxen, undated (Box 14)
    - American chestnut sample, Gaylord, Michigan, 1969; 2 photographic prints (Box 14)